<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>My site</title><link href="http://arnaudkaninda.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://arnaudkaninda.com/feeds/all-en.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://arnaudkaninda.com/</id><updated>2021-01-19T00:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>My first article</title><link href="http://arnaudkaninda.com/Test%20blog.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-19T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-01-19T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Arnaud Kaninda</name></author><id>tag:arnaudkaninda.com,2021-01-19:/Test blog.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Troisime  article pour tp&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Test arnaud kaninda 16
In january 19th  2021 a 20h:32
l a gunman entered a church in Sutherland Springs in Texas, where he killed 26 people and wounded 20 others. He escaped in his car, with police and residents in hot pursuit, before losing control …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Troisime  article pour tp&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Test arnaud kaninda 16
In january 19th  2021 a 20h:32
l a gunman entered a church in Sutherland Springs in Texas, where he killed 26 people and wounded 20 others. He escaped in his car, with police and residents in hot pursuit, before losing control of the vehicle and flipping it into a ditch. When the police got to the car, he was dead. The episode is horrifying enough without its unsettling epilogue. In the course of their investigations, the FBI reportedly pressed the gunman’s finger to the fingerprint-recognition feature on his iPhone in an attempt to unlock it. Regardless of who’s affected, it’s disquieting to think of the police using a corpse to break into someone’s digital afterlife.

Most democratic constitutions shield us from unwanted intrusions into our brains and bodies. They also enshrine our entitlement to freedom of thought and mental privacy. That’s why neurochemical drugs that interfere with cognitive functioning can’t be administered against a person’s will unless there’s a clear medical justification. Similarly, according to scholarly opinion, law-enforcement officials can’t compel someone to take a lie-detector test, because that would be an invasion of privacy and a violation of the right to remain silent.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My blog is under contruction, we will be back very sn&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="dev"></category></entry><entry><title>Test chat</title><link href="http://arnaudkaninda.com/test-chat.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-12-05T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-12-05T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Arnaud Kaninda</name></author><id>tag:arnaudkaninda.com,2020-12-05:/test-chat.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is a test of my chat&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="chat"></category></entry></feed>